# **DAVID ROA**UI Designer | Graphic Designer

UI designer with a graphic design background and experience in materializing ideas and guidelines with a user-centered focus. Skilled at creating compelling and intuitive user experiences using my illustration background.

## **Experience**

## Tango Discos y Libros

September 2020 - December 2020

- Conducted research on the company's branding and history to design bookmarks to complement their printed advertisement.
- Collaborated with stakeholders to conceptualize and design brandappropriate business cards.

## **Entre Rios y Montanas**

February 2020 - March 2020

- Collaborated with Colombian artist Luisa Roa to illustrate a map depicting the wildlife and vegetation in Caqueta (Colombia).
- Researched key elements and characteristics of Caqueta (Colombia) to create a faithful depiction of their ecosystems.
- Collaborated remotely with developers and stakeholders to follow the project's quidelines and deliver a cohesive product.

#### **Fusion Andina**

March 2015 - May 2015

- Designed business cards and menus following the company's guidelines and branding for the opening day of the restaurant.
- Developed two different iterations of menus and business cards and tested them with stakeholders to pick the design that best represents the company.

#### **Metropolis Boston**

April 2012 - August 2019

- Worked as a bartender prioritizing tasks and minding time constraints to deliver a timely experience for every customer at the bar.
- Created craft cocktails inspired by the current season of the year using ingredients and flavors that would best represent them.
- Collaborated with servers and kitchen staff to deliver a better product to the public.
- Translated in Spanish and English to create a more efficient team dynamic.

## Contact

857-3122349
Linkedin.com/in/davidroaUI
Davidroaui.myportfolio.com
Denver, CO

Davidroaf@gmail.com

## **Education**

**UI Design Program** CareerFoundry Denver, Colorado 2020

**Graphic Design** 

and Multimedia LaSalle College International Bogota, Colombia 2009

### **Skills**

#### Personal

Creativity
Team Work
Organization
Flexibility

#### Technical

Graphic Design
User-Centered Design
Rapid Ideation
Usability Testing
Responsive Web Design
Prototyping
Wireframing

#### Software

Sketch Figma Invsion Illustrator Photoshop Indesign

#### Languages

English Spanish